Joel Jang

Last updated on Jan 20, 2023

joeljang.github.io ♦ joeljang@kaist.ac.kr

RESEARCH INTERESTS

My main research goal is to build large neural models that are applicable to real-world scenarios, by addressing inherent limitations of current neural models. Specifically, I am interested in allowing neural models to be lifelong learners [C1, C2, P1], providing privacy and security guarantees for neural models [P2], and enabling neural models to follow the given instructions [W1, P3, P4].

EDUCATION

M.S. in Artificial Intelligence

Seoul, Korea

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

03/2021 - 08/2023

Graduate School of AI | Language & Knowledge Lab

Advisor: Minjoon Seo

B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering

Seoul, Korea

Korea University

03/2017 - 02/2021

PUBLICATIONS

Peer-Reviewed Conference Papers

[C2] TemporalWiki: A Lifelong Benchmark for Training and Evaluating Ever-Evolving Language Models **Joel Jang***, Seonghyeon Ye*, Changho Lee, Sohee Yang, Joongbo Shin, Janghoon Han, Gyeonghun Kim, Minjoon Seo

EMNLP 2022 [paper][code]

[C1] Towards Continual Knowledge Learning of Language Models

Joel Jang, Seonghyeon Ye, Sohee Yang, Joongbo Shin, Janghoon Han, Gyeonghun Kim, Stanley Jungkyu Choi, Minjoon Seo

ICLR 2022 [paper] [code]

Peer-Reviewed Workshop Papers

[W1] Can Large Language Models Truly Follow Your Instructions? Case-study with Negated Prompts **Joel Jang***, Seonghyeon Ye*, Minjoon Seo

NeurIPS 2022 Workshop on Transfer Learning for NLP (TL4NLP) [paper][code]

Peer-Reviewed Journal Papers

[J2] Sequential Targeting: A Continual Learning Approach for Data Imbalance in Text Classification **Joel Jang**, Yoonjeon Kim, Kyoungho Choi, Sungho Suh Expert Systems With Applications (2021) [paper] [code]

[J1] Supervised Health Stage Prediction Using Convolution Neural Networks for Bearing Wear Sungho Suh, **Joel Jang**, Seungjae Won, Mayank S. Jha, Yong Oh Lee Sensors (2020) [paper] [code]

Preprints

[P4] Retrieval of Soft Prompt Enhances Zero-shot Task Generalization Seonghyeon Ye, **Joel Jang.** Doyoung Kim, Yongrae Jo, Minjoon Seo *To Be Submitted to ACL 2023* [paper][code]

[P3] Guess the Instruction! Making Language Models Stronger Zero-shot Learners Seonghyeon Ye, Doyoung Kim, **Joel Jang**, Joongbo Shin, Minjoon Seo *Submitted to ICLR 2023* [paper][code]

[P2] Knowledge Unlearning for Mitigating Privacy Risks in Language Models **Joel Jang**, Dongkeun Yoon, Sohee Yang, Sungmin Cha, Moontae Lee, Lajanugen Logeswaran, Minjoon Seo *Submitted to ICLR 2023* [paper][code]

[P1] Prompt Injection: Parameterization of Fixed Inputs Eunbi Choi, Yongrae Jo, **Joel Jang**, Minjoon Seo *Submitted to ICLR 2023*, [paper][code]

EXPERIENCE

LG AI Research Seoul, Korea

Research Intern (Mentors: Moontae Lee, Lajanugen Logeswaran)

07/2022-Current

Working on (1) knowledge unlearning for LMs & (2) unseen task generalization with expert LMs

Kakao Brain Seongnam, Korea

Research Intern (Mentor: Ildoo Kim) 12/2020-02/2021

Worked on large-scale representation learning with weak supervision of images and caption data using TPUs

NAVER Seongnam, Korea

Software Engineer Intern

07/2020-09/2020

Worked on hate speech detection model, AI Clean Bot 2.0 (40+ million monthly users, >80% of Korean population) Developed novel method of handling data imbalance using continual learning (paper published under ESWA)

KIST Europe Saarbrucken, Germany

Research Intern (Mentor: Yong Oh Lee)

08/2019-01/2020

Worked on anomaly detection & remaining useful life prediction of machinery (paper published under Sensors) Gave an Oral Presentation at PHM Korea 2020 (2020. 07. 23)

SERVICES

Conference Reviewer

COLING 2022, EMNLP 2022, AKBC 2022, ICLR 2023, ACL 2023

Journal Reviewer

Journal of Artificial Intelligence Research (JAIR)

TEACHING

(KAIST AI599) AI for Law

09/2022-Current

Teaching Assistant (TA)

(KAIST AI605) Deep Learning for NLP

03/2022-06/2022

Teaching Assistant (TA)

INVITED TALKS

| Temporal Adaptation of Language Models Korean AI Association Summer NLP Session (Host: Minjoon Seo) | | 08/2022 |
|--|--------------------------------------|---------|
| | | |
| | | |
| Tempor | ral Adaptation of Language Models | 07/2022 |
| KAIST | School of Computing (Host: Alice Oh) | |
| | | |
| Tempor | ral Adaptation of Language Models | 05/2022 |
| Hyperc | connect (Host: Buru Chang) | |
| Нурегс | connect (Host: Buru Chang) | |

HONORS AND AWARDS

Qualcomm Innovation Fellowship Korea (QIFK) 2022
Grand Prize in Graduation Capstone Competition (Best Paper Award), 2020 (*Advisor: Jaewoo Kang*) 4th place, AI NLP Challenge Enliple Cup, 2020
3rd place, HAAFOR Challenge 2019
Future Global Leader Scholarships, Korea University, 2019
Best Innovation Award, Intel AI Drone Hackathon, 2018

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Bilingual in English (2004-2016 in US) and Korean (native)

GRE: 326 (Verbal, 157/170, 76th Percentile) | Quant, 169/170, 95th Percentile | Writing, 5.0/6.0, 92nd Percentile)

TOEFL: 119/120 (Reading, 30 | Listening, 30 | Speaking, 29 | Writing, 30)

SAT: 1530/1600 (Reading and Writing, 730 | Math, 800)